Guide to the Harry J. Rathbun Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Audiovisual recordings, Accession ARCH-2011-193
  - Myths for Moderns: Lecture 5, 5.42; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Myths for Moderns: Lecture 2, 5.43; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Myths for Moderns: Lecture 4, 5.44; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Beginning Teaching, 5.45; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, as the Teacher: Sermon on the Mt./King of God, 5.46; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Sermon on the Mount, 5.47; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Baptism and Wilderness, 5.48; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Sermon on the Mount/Kingdom of God, 5.49; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Teaching on Prayer, 5.50; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Entry into Jerusalem, 5.51; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus #3, 1975 Nov 3; 5.52; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Early Christian Church: Formation of the Church, 5.53; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Early Christian Church: Formation of the Church, 5.54; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Archetypes, 5.55; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Biblical Time Line & Dispensations, 5.56; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - I-Thou, 5.57; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Mary & Book 2 Thomas, 5.58; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Harry & Emilia Rathbun, Ben Lomond, 1983 Jul 8; 5.59; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Book of John-#5 Emilia, 1977 May 19; 5.60; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Meditation and Prayer: A Working Session, 1983 Apr 13; 5.61; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Living Meditation, 5.62; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Meditation and Prayer: A Working Session, 1983 Apr 13; 5.63; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Meditation and Prayer: A Working Session, 1983 Apr 13; 5.64; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Meditation and Prayer: A Working Session, 1983 Apr 13; 5.65; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Living Meditation and Prayer, 5.66; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Biblical Time Line & Dispensations, 5.67; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Book of John-#1 Emilia, 1977 Apr 7; 5.68; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Catherine Austin Fitts: About the Solari model, 2003 Jun 30; 5.69; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia - Saratoga Foothill Club, 1982 Apr 29; 5.70; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Claudio Naranjo, M.D.: "The Psychology of Enneatypes as a catalyst for change.", 2003 Aug; 5.71; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus #3, 1975 Nov 3; 5.72; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia-Saratoga Foothill Club, Session 3, 5.73; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Harry & Emilia Rathbun, Ben Lomond, 1983 Jul 8; 5.74; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia-Jesus Sermon, 1976; 5.75; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Book of Thrones, 3rd Meeting, 1976 Apr 19; 5.76; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia-Saratoga Foothill Club, 1982 Apr 22; 5.77; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia Rathbun-Ben Lomond, Foothill Area Leadership Weekend, 1986 Jan 11; 5.78; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - The New Religion: Contemporary Abstracts from the Old Myths: Saul & David, 5.79; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus #2, 1975 Oct 27; 5.80; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Principles for Designing New Social Forms, 2003 Jul 9; 5.81; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Amory Lovins "Natural Capitolism", 2001 Apr 19; 5.82; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Early Christian Church: Formation of the Church, 5.83; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Robert Theobald at FGC, 1999 Sep 16; 5.84; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - 1999 Speaker Series-Denis Hayes: "Preparing to Live in the Next Millenium", 1999 Oct 27; 5.85; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - 1999 Speaker Series-Joanna Macy: "Coming Back to Life: Practice to Reconnect Our Lives, Our World", 1999 May 26; 5.86; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Our American Democracy: "Can 'We the People' Save the Republic?" Craig Barnes, 2003 Feb 8; 5.87; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "The Food Revolution" How your Diet can help you save your Life and the World. John Robbins, 2001 Jul 26; 5.88; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Ursula Goodenough, author of "The Sacred Depths of Nature", 1999 Apr 30; 5.89; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Suddenly, Sustainability Counts," Paul H. Ray at Stanford Faculty Club, 2001 Jan 26; 5.90; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Sustainability Simplified," Catherine Gray and Laila Kaiser, 2000 Jul 28; 5.91; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Authority and Identity, 5.92; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Creating Sustainable Communities," Alan AtKisson, 2001 Feb 27; 5.93; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jean Shinoda Bolen, MD, "The Millionth Circle", 1999 Oct 13; 5.94; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Principles for Designing New Social Forms", 2003 Jul 9; 5.95; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - The Historical Jesus: Overview, 5.96; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Harry Rathbun, Ben Lomond, "Sharing things Meaningful to Him", 1986 Jan 11; 5.97; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Universarium," Stan Gibson, 2001 Feb 20; 5.98; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Six Vital Steps to Form A Cocreative Community," Barbara Marx Hubbard, 2000 Nov 14; 5.99; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "A Wisdom for our Time." Paul Ray and Sherry Anderson, 2001 Jan 25; 5.100; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Daughterhood and Sustainability: A Polycultural Inquiry." Rachel Bagby, 2000 Oct 24; 5.101; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "A Conversation that Matters" with Sarah Van Gelder, 1999 Jul 9; 5.102; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Cradle to Cradle Design" Dr. Michael Braungart at Stanford University, 2005 Feb 16; 5.103; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Amory Lovins "Natural Capitolism" Stanford University, 2001 Apr 19; 5.104; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Cradle to Cradle Design" Dr. Michael Braungart at Stanford University, 2005 Feb 16; 5.105; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Retreat Review, 2001 Feb 22; 5.106; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "A Conversation that Matters" with Sarah Van Gelder, 1999 Jul 9; 5.107; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Turning the Tide" Staff Meeting. Tom Burt, Catherine Parrish, Joe Kressee, Richard Rathbun., 2000 Nov 21; 5.108; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - The New Religion: Contemporary Abstracts from the Old Myths: Feminine Principle, 5.109; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - The New Religion: Contemporary Abstracts from the Old Myths: Job, 5.110; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Authority and Identity, 5.111; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Dr. Karl-Henrik Robert, "The Natural Step", 2002 May 8; 5.112; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Natural Capitalism" L. Hunter Lovins and Walter Link., 2002 Mar 11; 5.112; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Sister Miriam MacGillis at Sequoia Seminar, 1999 Jan 30-31; 5.113; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - FGC/Afghan Center Wash. D.C. Trip; Discussion (Tape 1), 2001 Nov 12-16, 2001 Nov 29; 5.114; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - FGC/Afghan Center Wash. D.C. Trip; Discussion (Tape 2), 2001 Nov 12-16, 2001 Nov 29; 5.115; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Early Christian Church, 5.116; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Designing Like Nature," William McDonough, 2001 Nov 14; 5.117; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "The Human Story: Transforming the root causes of violence." Robert Keck, Ph.D., 2001 Nov 9; 5.118; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Duane Elgin, "Promise Ahead: Humanity's Journey Toward a Culture of Meaning.", 2000 May 10; 5.119; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Speaker Series: "How Modern Cosmology can Nourish the Spiritual Imagination." Joel Primack and Nancy Ellen Abrams., 2000 Feb 2; 5.120; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Sustaining Our Planet: A review of world resource use, limits, and necessary change." Martin Squiibbs., 2000 Feb 9; 5.121; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus, The Teacher: Authority and Identity, 5.122; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia Rathbun & Steve Crothers on "Love and Knowledge.", 1996 Feb 15; 5.123; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Sister Miriam MacGillis at Sequoia Semiar, 1999 Jan 30-31; 5.124; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jesus #5, 1975 Nov 17; 5.125; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "What can Nature teach us about Sustainable Business?" Janine Benyus, 2003 Jan 29; 5.126; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Sustainability Made Real" Gail Brownell, Agilent, 2001 Sep 14; 5.127; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Emilia - Dreams, 1979 Jan 8; 5.128; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "The Moral Architecture of World Peace." Helena Cobban, 2000 Sep 26; 5.129; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Economics As If The Earth Matters" Joe Kresse, 2000 Oct 11; 5.130; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Psychology of the Future," Stanislav Grof, M.D., 2000 Jul 6; 5.131; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Angeles Arrien, "Polishing the soul: Generativity, Intimacy, and Creativity", 1999 Mar 30; 5.132; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Hope's Edge: With food as our teacher, We can learn to see with new eyes." Frances Moore Lappe., 2001 Oct 17; 5.133; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Meditation and Prayer (Emilia to P.O. Men), 1983 Apr 15; 5.134; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Local Food, Global Prosperity" Amuradha Mittal, 2003 Feb 19; 5.135; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - "Fixing Elections" Steven Hill, 2003 May 29; 5.135; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Working Session on Meditation and Prayer (Emilia to P.O. Men), 1983 Apr 15; 5.135; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Principles for Designing New Social Forms, 2003 Jul 9; 5.136; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Harry Rathbun Lecture, 1955; 5.137; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 5)
  - [unlabeled], 5.138; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
- Audio recordings, Accession ARCH-2014-085
  - Sequoia Seminar - lecture announcement, 1.0 (Box 1, 1, Folder 1, 1)
  - Man and His Self Fulfillment, 1965 Jan 16; 1.1; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 1)
  - The Mature Man and the Good Society, 1955 Jan 23; 1.2; 1 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 1)
  - Lecture II Man and His Self Fulfillment, 1.3; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)
  - Lecture III The Mature Man and the Good Society, 1.4; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)
  - Questions and Answers, 1.5; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)
  - Tape 1, 1.6; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)
  - Tape 2 Part B, 1.7; 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1)